Brandon Sovran

50 Woodgate Drive, Toronto, ON M6N 4W3 | 647-201-7706 | Brandon.Sovran@gmail.com

February 28, 2019

Dear Hiring Team:

I am a hardworking, self-motivated and reliable individual very interested in joining your team. I am currently successfully completing my first year of studies at McGill University, pursuing a degree in computer science. I am an honours graduate of Humberside C.I. (French Immersion) and Ontario Scholar. My career goal is to apply my passion, knowledge and skills in the field of software development.

Over the years I have consistently maintained a very high academic standard (95%) while pursuing entrepreneurial opportunities in website development and performing lawn maintenance services for seniors as well as seasonal employment with the Canadian National Exhibition. In addition, I have been an avid participant in competitive sports including hockey, rugby, lacrosse, soccer and ski racing. Combined, these experiences have allowed me to develop very strong time management and problem-solving skills; strengthened my ability to work well with others as part of a team and to be a good self-starter and to take initiative on tasks.

Thank you for consideration of my application. I am very confident that through my strong work ethic and approachable personality, I will be a great addition to your team.

I look forward to hearing from you.

Sincerely,

Brandon Bovran

Brandon Sovran

BRANDON SOVRAN

50 Woodgate Drive Toronto, Ontario, M6N 4W3 647.201.7706 (m), 416.763.4791 (h) Brandon.Sovran@gmail.com

CAREEER GOAL – SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

McGill University, Montreal (Computer Science), Freshman Year, September 2018

• Faculty of Science, Honours Software Engineering stream

Humberside C.I, TDSB (Grades 9-12), September 2014 to June 2018

- French-Immersion Certificate; OSSD; Ontario Scholar
- Honour Roll (every term); Mathematics and Computer Science Achievement Awards

WORK EXPERIENCE

General Maintenance – **C.N.E.,** August 2018

Provided general cleaning maintenance and operated compacting equipment (Food Building).

Website Developer/Consultant – Self-Employed, January 2014 to present

- Over the years I have helped others create and enhance their online businesses.
 Independently I create and modify websites using html to give the best product to my clients.
- Former clients include: Greenways Landscaping and Snow Removal; Greenway Construction;
 Sherwin Nicholson-independent author.

Lawn Maintenance – Self-Employed, 2013 to 2017 (Seasonal)

- Cut and trimmed home lawns for senior citizens.
- Able to work outdoors in various weather conditions.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Camp Counselor - City of Toronto, Clairville Summer Camp, July 2015

Responsible for helping with program for young children at full-day camp.

Special Events Assistant – Baby Point Club Ltd., 2014 to 2016

Responsible for helping organise children's games and club dinners.

ACHIEVEMENTS and RECOGNITIONS

2017	University of Toronto Chemistry Scholars
2017	University of Waterloo Computing Contest – High Achievement
2016	Humberside C.I Rugby 7's Most Valuable Player